如果你在手机上跑这个程序的话  你的应用程序将会崩溃
If you run it on your phone, your app will crashed
因为报 NetworkOnMainException 错误了
because of a network got main thread exception. We found
我们通过连接手机和电脑
this answer by connecting our device to our computer and
通过工具来检查错误
then checking Android device monitor for the error. You can
左边你能看到的是我们的包名
see here that this is our package name and this
和进程号  如果你在这里搜索那个进程号
is our process ID. If you search the logs for
然后我们的错误就显示出来了  我们（从Caused by这里）能发现它
that process ID then our error appears. It's triggered ultimately
最终报的错是NetworkOnMainThreadException
by a network on main thread exception. If you're curious
如果你想确定是哪行代码出错了
as to what line of our code actually caused
你可以继续下拉查看更多
this, you can scroll down the stack trace to
这一部分是我们的框架部分
read more. This is our framework code that you
你可以直接跳到我们自己代码的这个部分
can skip and here's where it actually hits our
在PlaceholderFragment这个类的onCreateView()方法里报错了
app. It's within the placeholder fragment class, in the onCreateView method. And
它在 MainActivity.java 这个文件的第116行
it happens in main activity.java file, in line 116. So
所以我们回到我们的代码里去  116行是urlConnection.connect()这个方法引起了错误
if we go back to the code, on that line you can see that urlConnection.connect
实际上我们不能在主线程上执行它喔
actually caused the error, and that we can't do that on the main thread.